<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>RidwanBejo Dev</title>
    <link>https://ridwanbejo.github.io/</link>
    <description>Recent content on RidwanBejo Dev</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>© ridwanbejo 2022</copyright>
    
	<atom:link href="https://ridwanbejo.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>About Me</title>
      <link>https://ridwanbejo.github.io/about-me/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ridwanbejo.github.io/about-me/</guid>
      <description>Hi, I am Ridwan Fadjar Septian. I am a passionate IT Engineer who took specialization in software (backend) and cloud infrastructure engineering. I have hands-on experience for 8+ years. Currently, I am living in Indonesia.
I have interests in DevOps, cloud infrastructure development, high scalable systems, serverless computing, container orchestration, IT governance, IT security and many more. My favorite quote is: &amp;ldquo;Customer satisfaction is first priority&amp;rdquo;.
Currently, I am working as Cloud Infrastructure Engineer at NiceDay Nederland B.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Achievements</title>
      <link>https://ridwanbejo.github.io/achievements/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ridwanbejo.github.io/achievements/</guid>
      <description>I have completed some training or courses. Here they are.
Completion Badges  Google Cloud Skill Boost Badges Microsoft Learn Badges LeetCode Badges  Training or Courses 2022
 Coursera - Site Reliability Engineering: Measuring and Managing Reliability by Google Cloud Coursera - Architecting with Google Kubernetes Engine Specialization by Google Cloud  2021
 Dicoding - Architecting on AWS (Membangun Arsitektur Cloud di AWS) by Dicoding Indonesia Dicoding - Cloud Practitioner Essentials (Belajar Dasar AWS Cloud) by Dicoding Indonesia Redis University - (FREE) RU301: Running Redis at Scale Redis University - (FREE) RU330: Redis Security by Redis Lab Redis University - (FREE) RU101: Introduction to Redis Data Structures by Redis Lab Cockroach University - (FREE) Introduction to Distributed SQL and CockroachDB by Cockroach Lab Udemy - (FREE) Linux Operating System Fundamentals by Linux Academy  2019</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Certification</title>
      <link>https://ridwanbejo.github.io/certification/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ridwanbejo.github.io/certification/</guid>
      <description>Currently, I am certified as:
 Google Cloud Platform - Cloud Digital Leader  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Contacts</title>
      <link>https://ridwanbejo.github.io/contacts/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ridwanbejo.github.io/contacts/</guid>
      <description>You can reach me by online through:
 E-Mail LinkedIn Github Medium Dev.to Aku.dev  If you are interested to my photography works, reach me through:
 Instagram PicFair Photocrowd  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>My Projects</title>
      <link>https://ridwanbejo.github.io/my-projects/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ridwanbejo.github.io/my-projects/</guid>
      <description>I open some my personal projects in Github. You may access those projects here:
 Ansible Modules for Sentry 10 -&amp;gt; click here Helm Charts for Jim Merioles Weather App -&amp;gt; click here My homepage powered by Hugo -&amp;gt; click here  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Publications</title>
      <link>https://ridwanbejo.github.io/publications/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ridwanbejo.github.io/publications/</guid>
      <description>You can access my publications for internal conference here:
 A Study Review of Common Big Data Architecture for Small-medium Enterprise | EAI - European Union Digital Library | Proceeding Risk Analysis of Dutch Healthcare Company Information System | IOP Conference Series: Materials Science and Engineering, Volume 662, Issue 2 | Proceeding  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Talks</title>
      <link>https://ridwanbejo.github.io/talks/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ridwanbejo.github.io/talks/</guid>
      <description>I used to be speaker in some meetup or conferences such as:
 Django Application Monitoring and Logging with Sentry, ELK (Elasticsearch, Logstash &amp;amp; Kibana) and Prometheus (Online). PyCon Indonesia Regular Talk - 2021 | Page | Slide Introduction to AWS SQS for Web Application Task Queue (Online). AWS User Group Indonesia Meetup - 2020 | Slide Introduction to DevOps (Online). CS Meetup by Ilmu Komputer UPI - 2020 | Slide Why Serverless?</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>