<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>RidwanBejo Dev</title>
    <link>https://ridwanbejo.github.io/</link>
    <description>Recent content on RidwanBejo Dev</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>Ridwanbejo Dev</copyright><atom:link href="https://ridwanbejo.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>About Me</title>
      <link>https://ridwanbejo.github.io/about-me/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ridwanbejo.github.io/about-me/</guid>
      <description>Hi, I am Ridwan Fadjar. I am a passionate IT Engineer who took specialization in software (backend) and cloud infrastructure engineering. I have hands-on experience for 9+ years. Currently, I am living in Indonesia. I have interests in DevOps, cloud infrastructure development, high scalable systems, serverless computing, container orchestration, IT governance, IT security and many more.
Currently, I am working as Cloud Infrastructure Engineer at DKatalis Digital Lab which building end-to-end financial system in Indonesia.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Achievements</title>
      <link>https://ridwanbejo.github.io/achievements/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ridwanbejo.github.io/achievements/</guid>
      <description>I have completed some training or courses. Here they are.
Training or Courses 2023
Udemy - GitLab CI - A Complete Hands-On for CI/CD Pipelines &amp;amp; DevOps by A to Z Mentors Udemy - Istio Hands-On for Kubernetes by Richard Chesterwood Udemy - Kubernetes Certified Application Developer (CKAD) with Tests by Mumshad Mannambeth 2022
Udemy - Certified Kubernetes Administrator (CKA) with Practice Tests by Mumshad Mannambeth Udemy - Jenkins, From Zero To Hero: Become a DevOps Jenkins Master by Ricardo Andre Gonzalez Gomez Google Cloud Skill Boost Badges Microsoft Learn Skill Badges Coursera - Site Reliability Engineering: Measuring and Managing Reliability by Google Cloud Coursera - Architecting with Google Kubernetes Engine Specialization by Google Cloud 2021</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Certification</title>
      <link>https://ridwanbejo.github.io/certification/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ridwanbejo.github.io/certification/</guid>
      <description>Currently, I am certified as:
Google Cloud Platform - Associate Cloud Engineer Google Cloud Platform - Cloud Digital Leader </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Contacts</title>
      <link>https://ridwanbejo.github.io/contacts/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ridwanbejo.github.io/contacts/</guid>
      <description>You can reach me by online through:
Github Medium </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>My Projects</title>
      <link>https://ridwanbejo.github.io/my-projects/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ridwanbejo.github.io/my-projects/</guid>
      <description>I open some my personal projects in Github. You may access those projects here.
2023:
terraform-airflow-config - Terraform module for managing Apache Airflow Variables, Pools and Connections -&amp;gt; click here terraform-airflow-user - Terraform module for managing Apache Airflow Users and Roles -&amp;gt; click here terraform-iam-user-group - Terraform module for managing AWS IAM Users, Roles, Policies and Groups -&amp;gt; click here Plausible - Python API Wrapper for Plausible API -&amp;gt; click here Kubus - Kubernetes security scanner prototype based on CIS benchmark -&amp;gt; click here 2022:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Publications</title>
      <link>https://ridwanbejo.github.io/publications/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ridwanbejo.github.io/publications/</guid>
      <description>You can access my publications for internal conference here:
A Study Review of Common Big Data Architecture for Small-medium Enterprise | EAI - European Union Digital Library | Proceeding Risk Analysis of Dutch Healthcare Company Information System | IOP Conference Series: Materials Science and Engineering, Volume 662, Issue 2 | Proceeding </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Talks</title>
      <link>https://ridwanbejo.github.io/talks/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ridwanbejo.github.io/talks/</guid>
      <description>I used to be speaker in some meetup or conferences such as:
Cloud Infrastructure Engineer vs SRE. Alchemy x DKatalis online meetup - 2023 Cloud Infrastructure Automation with Python. BandungPy Offline Meetup - 2023 | Page Django Application Monitoring and Logging with Sentry, ELK (Elasticsearch, Logstash &amp;amp; Kibana) and Prometheus (Online). PyCon Indonesia Regular Talk - 2021 | Page | Slide Introduction to AWS SQS for Web Application Task Queue (Online).</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
